itechhacks.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or take action on **https://itechhacks.com** (the “Site”).

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

 **We collect Device Information using the following technologies:**

– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and

how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org./)

– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

– “ **Google Analytics** ” which gives us your [site](https://itechhacks.com/) usage information

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, PayPal), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

 **How we use collected information?**

iTech Hacks may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

1\. To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

2\. To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.

3\. To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

Below every email we send with your permission, there’s a link attached to unsubscribe yourself.

 **How we protect your information?**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

 **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

By accessing the services and/or completing the registration process for itechhacks.com website, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older. In simpler words, you have to be at least 18 years old to access our website and use its services.

 **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

You may opt out of personalized advertising from Google by visiting  
<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at

<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

 **Push Notifications**

When you visit itechhacks.com, you might receive a pop-up asking for your permission to send you to push notifications on your device. In case you choose not to agree, you can continue using our website. If you choose to agree to receive push notifications on your device, you can later opt-out of the notifications by searching for “Notifications” in your web browser’s “Settings” section. Find more information on One Signal’s push notification service here:

<https://onesignal.com/privacy_policy>

Reproduction and use:

The users acknowledge and agree that all copyright and trademarks and other intellectual property rights in the Website and all material or content related to the website shall remain, at all times, owned by itechhacks Media and/or their respective owners. All material and content contained is made available for the user’s personal and non-commercial use only. Any other use of the material/content on the platform is strictly prohibited.

All the information, all without special notice, the copyright belongs to M/s itechhacks Media. In case any material which is approved by itechhacks is approved, it must be marked with the source of the document and full credits to the copyright owners should be given. If any person is found to be in infringement of this requirement, the offender shall be held accountable according to law.

iTechHacks shall hold the right to modify and update the copyrighted material at any time.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

itechhacks has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a **European resident** we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

 **MINORS**

The Site is intended for individuals under the age of 12.

 **CHANGES**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

 **Contacting us**

iTechHacks is committed to providing a secure and transparent experience to our Users. Protecting our Users’ privacy and data is extremely important to us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at **admin@itechhacks.com**

Headquartered at Himachal Pradesh, 177001, India
